(MV)由Letupita725HD(Youtube)制作
All Good
马迷自制MV
Get in the groove
节奏带入
You bring your dancing shoes
你把舞鞋穿出
I'll bring the attitude
我展示这态度
You bring the crew so we can move
一起跳舞展示舞步
Light up the floor
舞池闪烁
Turn up the bass
弹起这贝斯
Yeah, let me see that smile on your face
耶，尽情展示笑容的美
Come on and go with the flow
随着人流一起走
Gonna steal the show, yeah
准备抢风头，耶
Let me show you how it goes
我给大家露一手
Repeat after me!
一二预备起！
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
Hey! Throw your hands up higher
嘿 把手都举着
Turn up the amplifier
调高音量不忐忑
Watch me I'm on fire, fire
看我状态火热，火热
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴
Hey! Throw your hands up higher
嘿 把手都举着
Turn up the amplifier
调高音量不忐忑
Watch me I'm on fire, fire
看我状态火热，火热
'Cause it's all, all, all, all good
我们多，多，多，么酷
I feel abso-absolutely amazing
这美妙的感觉真令人高兴